Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Didn't discharge their weapons.
wore gloves the entire time.
And as we know. they all wore prosthetics.
so our facial recognition software
is completely useless.
IRU tracked their exit on CCTV.
They took public transport
and then they split up.
And then they all disappeared
into camera blackspots.
We checked how they paid their fares.
Debit cards. All of them cloned.
The level they're operating at.
the professionalism.
we're talking ex-army.
ex-special services. maybe state actors.
There's two strands to this. guys.
Find the thieves. Find the money.
As you know. both are time-critical.
so we need to move at warp speed. Yeah?
Four billion. the UK's biggest ever
robbery and it's people's pensions. okay?
Speak to your DS's
about divvying up the video work.
- Any news on the account numbers yet?
- Still nothing.
Should come through soon. though.
Commissioner's putting the pressure on.
I think that's our guy.
- DI Ellie Lloyd.
- DI Lloyd. I'm Darren Yoshida. I'm your...
- Nice to meet you.
- Yeah.
Hi. er. DCI Cov...
- Covaci.
I'm. er. Darren Yoshida.
your Financial Investigator.
- Took your time.
- Erm. sorry?
You should have been here
yesterday afternoon.
Well. I. er.
was assigned the case an hour ago.
I came straight here. So...
- An hour ago?
- Yeah.
So much for warp speed.
- Let's get you started.
- Yep.
Now...
We don't yet know exactly
what was taken. or indeed how much.
But the fact this raid...
- ID. please.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
Is there a risk individual
customers might lose their pensions?
That is the question...
Morning.
And if people have lost their
pensions. will they get compensation?
- What?
- And if so. who's going to pay it?
- We need to talk.
- Thank you. George.
That was George Ainsworth...
Five million? What are you...
They said a hundred grand!
- Luke. you need to check your account.
- Five million...
Luke! You need to take the crypto
from your account.
put it on the cold wallet. Offline.
Sure. and then I've got a bloody
crypto wallet with five million...
Which you can hide! Okay?
If you leave the money online. then
there's a trail between us and them!
We need to do exactly what they told us.
which actually. by the way.
you should have done already.
Use a VPN
to log onto your online account.
move the money.
hide it. close the account.
They've done this on purpose.
You realise they've done this
so it looks like we were involved.
We were involved. Okay? Just 'cause
they said it was gonna be a hack.
and that we only had to give
our login details. does not...
- Hello. mate!
- Mate.
- Hey.
- How's it?
Pretty mental. eh?
Josh said. on his way in.
some journalist offered him five grand
for office photos and a bit of gossip.
Stop. What gossip?
- I don't know.
- Oh.
So. you two are gonna have
your work cut out. eh?
Why?
Because we've got
a £4 billion hole in portfolios.
It's good of you to come in. though.
and help with it all.
I mean. if that was me.
gun pointed to my head.
I would've taken
the next six months off with stress.
Yeah. well. it's an emergency. right?
All hands on deck.
Mm-hm.
- Cheers.
- Cheers. Wayne.
What the fuck?
What the fuck was that? He suspects.
- Everyone suspects.
- No. no. no. they don't.
- Yes...
- They have no reason to.
There's no evidence.
Apart from the ten million quids'
worth of pensions that we now own!
Okay. I know. I know. I know.
- We have go to the police.
- What?
It's the only way. It's...
We have to say that we were duped
and that we just thought we were giving
business details over to a rival...
What do you think they'll do
if we go to the police?
- You saw what they did to Jason and Donny.
- So. what the fuck do we do?
- Right now...
- Luke.
- Hey.
- The detectives from yesterday are here.
conducting a few follow-up interviews.
They asked if they could speak with you.
So. what. they're here? Cool. Um...
Yeah. why-why do they
want to speak to... me?
'Cause. sorry.
I spoke to them yesterday.
- Follow-up interviews.
- Oh. yeah. you said that.
It's not a problem. is it?
I said you could use room six.
Yeah. that's...
I'm so busy with the. um...
Just like the rebalancing
and the transfers right now. it's...
Obviously. yeah.
Yeah. I'll be there in a minute.
Whatever they need. All good. Cool.
I'll see you both
at the trauma counselling session later.
Oh yeah. yeah. Can't wait for that.
What did you say to them
in your interview yesterday?
Nothing! I think
I just spent the whole thing crying.
Fuck's sake. don't admit anything. okay?
We need to really
think it through and also. if you confess.
we'll spend the rest of our lives
in prison or we'll end up dead. Okay?
Okay.
- Luke. come in.
- How's it going?
Have a seat.
Morning.
Er. Myrtle.
Didn't expect to see you today.
Are you kidding me?
Did you see all the press outside?
My mate WhatsApped me.
I was in the background on the news.
- walking into the office.
- Ah!
Look.
Mmm! Yeah. cool.
So cool.
Thank you for talking to us again.
We know how much work you have
dealing with the aftermath.
Yeah.
To tell you the truth
I'm impressed you turned up at all.
Yeah. well. it's an emergency. right?
All hands on deck.
Ellie. you met yesterday.
This is Darren Yoshida.
He's an accredited Financial Investigator.
Prior to the police. Darren
was an investment manager in the City.
which should hopefully give him
a good insight into what happened.
Cool.
Er... Yeah. so. just a few technical
questions. if that's all right?
First up. the. er. the four billion
in your cash account.
That's a pretty large chunk
of your AUM. isn't it?
Mm.
Do you usually have
that much sitting in cash?
Oh. er. no. No. no. it was just. we were
doing. er. a portfolio rebalancing.
Er. just a pretty big one.
You do that often?
Erm...
Probably every couple of years.
So. the thieves just happened to strike
on the single week in the last three years
that you've had the money sitting in cash?
Er. yeah. Yeah. I guess so. yeah.
Er. I am going to pop to the loo now.
Last catch-up question.
Just to confirm. the thieves.
they needed the Investment Committee
- to sign off the trades. right? Yeah?
- Mmm.
There just happened to be
an Investment Committee meeting
the morning of the robbery?
Yeah. Well. er. yeah.
But. um. to be fair. it's...
You know. they happen once a week.
So. there's like a...
a one-in-five chance.
- Luke.
- Mm?
Is there anything you wanna tell us?
These are dangerous people.
They put two of your colleagues
in hospital.
They were carrying automatic weapons
and the way they were handling them
suggests they're professionals.
Ruthless. Cold-blooded.
But us. we can protect you. Luke.
You just need to give me the word.
Er...
I think that's... Just thinking.
Yeah. that's everything.
I've told you everything I know so. um...
if that's all. am I good to go? Please?
Thanks for taking the time.
We really appreciate it.
Cheers. Sorry. Er. thank you.
Cheers. thanks.
If I was planning this
and wanted an inside man.
I'd go for someone
on the trade processing team.
Told you.
You're planning a heist like this.
you don't let it all rest
on someone like Luke.
They cultivated a backup. too.
Either way. we don't have enough
to arrest him yet.
I'll talk to the Super about surveillance.
They know. All right? They know.
Every question they were asking me
was like an accusation.
And they've got this. this finance guy.
this expert in there.
Just. everything I could say.
he knew I was bullshitting. okay?
I knew they knew. They fucking know!
Keep your voice down.
- Yo.
- Hey!
Hey.
- Are you two coming to the trauma thing?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. sure.
- We're going there now.
- Course. yeah.
- It's. like. starting now.
Yeah. We'll be along in a minute.
- Yeah.
I'm not going to the trauma thing.
I just wanted to say that
I think it's amazing that Lochmill
has arranged for these sessions.
It... It really shows how much they care
about their employees.
Oh. and I also wanted to thank Zara.
Like. you basically
put your life on the line for me
when you tried to get the thieves
to ignore me.
And when you took the call
from the custodian bank.
I think. like. you might have saved
all of our lives.
And I just want to thank you.
Zara. it sounds like
you were really central to all of this.
but you've not really spoken much yet.
Is there anything you'd like to share?
I... I guess I just...
Sorry.
Er...
I mean. I guess I just feel the same
as everyone else here.
You know. everything everyone's said
about their traumas
and everything we went through...
Okay. Thank you. Zara.
Who else?
Luke? What about you?
Erm...
I am still feeling pretty traumatised.
Um...
Probably too traumatised to talk.
Of course.
Of course. that's all right. Luke.
We've all gotta come to this
in our own time.
I guess the thing
that I'm feeling. right now.
is I feel scared to go outside
knowing that they're still on the street.
I feel like none of us are safe any more.
I don't know about you lot.
but I. you know. don't feel safe.
I don't feel safe at all and...
No. I don't know
that I'll ever feel safe again.
Thank you. thank you.
- What you just did...
- Fuck off. Fuck off. Fuck off.
No. we can use it. We can use it.
Guv? Got a minute?
I'll catch you later.
What the hell's going on?
Excuse me?
Darren Yoshida.
The Financial Investigator.
He should have been assigned within
two hours of us making the request.
- Instead...
- We were trying to get you
the best there is. And we did.
Is that it? Because I have
somewhere else I need to be.
Lochmill and the custodian bank.
They still haven't given up
the account details we need.
You said you were putting the pressure on.
How are you not moving at full pelt?
My team is.
Rhys...
There are more important things
going on here than you're aware of.
More important than thousands of people
losing their pensions?
Just remember. Tomorrow morning.
call in sick with stress.
I mean. you already announced to half
the company how distressed you are.
They won't suspect.
Then tonight. soon as you get home.
use the VPN to download the money
onto the cold wallet.
leave the flat.
stash it somewhere safe. Okay?
Then after that.
all you've gotta do is chill.
Keep your head down. Don't call me.
And above all...
Yeah. don't call the police.
I'll keep an eye on things this end.
Anything happens. I'll let you know.
We're gonna get through this. okay?
Just follow the plan.
Custodian bank finally got back to us.
The accounts the money was sent to.
- This is where the money is?
- No. it's where the money was sent.
To accounts at this bank.
but no idea whose accounts yet.
Willemstad Bank and Trust.
British Virgin Islands?
- I've never heard of it.
- Well. no reason you should have.
It's a private bank
in a notorious tax haven.
It'll be like a Swiss bank.
Small. Discrete. Super-rich.
If we know where the money is.
can't we just reverse the transaction?
We can't take money out
of someone's account in another country.
I'll put in a request
to contact the authorities
in the British Virgin Islands via the FIU.
get some details.
What's the timeframe for a response?
- Two to three weeks. normally.
- Two to three weeks?
Because all their other cases
are more important?
How do we speed things up?
Erm. political pressure.
Diplomatic Services.
Foreign Office. Bank of England.
It'll need to be quick.
The money won't stay there long.
Maybe it's already gone.
Yeah. maybe.
Two Bravo. I have eyes on subject.
In his building. he's at his window.
Looks like
he's surveying the street. Over.
Copy that. Two Bravo. Over.
Fuck.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Scratch card?
It's not like you.
Yeah. actually. Fuck it.
Yeah. I'll take one.
I just wanted to er.
see how you are.
It's all just been a bit. erm. shit
at the moment.
And it...
got me thinking
about fixing things between us.
Oh. right. yeah.
Patch it up with your mother
and that's one less thing to stress about.
Well. I suppose. yes. Is that so bad?
No. Course not. It's nice to know
I made it onto the "to-do" list.
Am I before or after cleaning the gutters?
Fuck's sake. Mum. Why do you have to
twist everything around?
- Every single time I try I come...
- Yeah. I'm so sorry.
If I'd have known you were coming.
I'd have rolled out the red carpet.
So. why's it all a bit shit at the moment?
Oh. God! That doesn't look like
my delivery. sorry.
Hang on a minute.
No. that's not everything.
- I should have at least two of those.
- That's everything on the list.
It's a mistake.
What the fuck are you doing?
Just came to use the loo and...
I don't know.
What. you got nostalgic?
More on the robbery
at Lochmill Capital.
Police confirmed earlier today
that the amount stolen
from the pensions manager
was in excess of £4 billion.
making it the largest armed robbery
in British history.
The funds were taken yesterday morning
in a daring raid
with intruders gaining entry to the office
and forcing staff at gunpoint
to transfer money
from the company's accounts.
Following the heist.
Lochmill Capital released a statement
saying it was working with police
and was setting up a contact centre
for anyone concerned about what happened.
Evening. Jimmy. Busy tonight?
Not yet. The stars are on their way.
Off you go.
Have a good night.
Hey. Luke.
Zara. it's me. sorry.
I know you said not to call but...
I did not say that.
It's the cold wallet.
I've done the transfer.
but I can't go outside to stash it
because they're outside.
And I can't hide it in here
because of the bugs.
So. what the fuck do I do?
Luke. What bugs?
What are you talking about?
I think they're watching me. Zara.
I think they've bugged my flat.
Fuck! It's game over. we're done!
- We're done.
- No. Luke. I think you are...
I think you're stressed.
I have to call the police. I...
No. no. no. Do not call the police!
You don't need the police. Luke.
You need a doctor
or a counsellor or just a mate. okay?
Because I think you're clearly stressed
and traumatised.
And you're not really
making any sense right now.
But it's okay. Just stay where you are.
I'm gonna come over. Okay?
Yeah.
Yeah. you're right. I'll stay here
and I'll find the bugs.
I'll find the cameras. yeah.
I'll wait for you. I'll find them.
Okay. I'm gonna be there
as soon as I can. okay?
Just go and lie down
and try to take your mind off.
I told you he was gonna get worse.
He's a liability.
We need to take him out. Now.
The unmarked police car's
still round the back.
Then there's that car. obviously.
And the foot tracker's
by the hotel down the road.
So. we're good to go?
We're good to go.
Copy that. Moving out.
- Pizza delivery.
- I didn't order anything.
- You're number 48?
- Yeah. I didn't order anything.
Fuck's sake.
This is the third time this week.
Look. listen. brother.
do you want the pizzas for a tip?
I'll just be throwing them away otherwise.
No. thanks. Sorry.
All right.
Cops are gonna notice
if he doesn't get in there soon.
Yeah. fuck it. All right then.
I'm on the seventh floor.
He's inside. Go.
Zero. seven.
Not like you to "hit and run".
I'm not running. Jimmy. I'm strolling.
DCI Covaci.
Hi. Hi. it's um. Luke.
Can I talk to you about some things?
Hi. Luke. Are you okay?
Yeah. I don't wanna talk about it
on the phone. can you come here?
Luke. if you've got something important
to tell me. please tell me now.
- I promise you...
- Could you come here?
Come here.
I don't wanna talk about it on the phone.
Luke. if it's important...
Just come here! Come here please!
Come here!
Okay. Okay. Sure. I'm heading off now.
- You're in Canary Wharf. right?
- Yes!
I've got your address. I'm leaving now.
In the meantime. stay inside. stay safe.
See you in a bit.
He's coming on his own from Bishopsgate.
That gives us seven minutes.
- Guv?
- Hello. mate.
I had a call from our subject
asking me to come for a chat.
He sounded agitated.
Anything happening there?
All quiet.
Check with the unit
at the back of the building.
Make sure everything's okay.
I'll be there in ten. 15 tops.
Xray to Bravo One Alpha.
Do a walk-past
of the subject building. Over.
Copy that. One Alpha.
Can you pull over here. please?
Keep the change.
Food delivery. Hello?
What the fuck. help!
Ah!
No! Ah! Help!
Xray Two Bravo One Alpha.
Do another walk past. Over.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-